Oh, I gotta hurry up!
Надо поторопиться!
Kosuke-sama.
Коске.
Izayoi-san.
Изайой.
Here you go.
Вот.
Thank you!
Спасибо.
Ai-san.
Ай.
Chi-Chika-chan, my back.
Чика, моя спина...
Alley-oop.
Раз-два, взяли!
Minami-chan, you rock!
Минами, круто!
Fear not my minions! More people in the house will not mean less food for you! I'll make sure of it!
Уши навострили! Больше народу — не значит, что еды нам будет меньше. Я прослежу за этим!
Yes? Sazanami Girls' Dorm.
Да? Женское общежитие Сазанами.
SubDESU-H Presents Triangle Heart Sazanami Girls Dorm
СЕРДЕЧНЫЙ ТРЕУГОЛЬНИК Женское общежитие Сазанами
Huh?
Чего?
I-I'm Makihara Kosuke from the Sazanami Girls' Dorm.
Я из общежития Сазанами, Макихара Коске!
Ah! Good afternoon! Pleased to meet you. I'm Shiina.
Добрый вечер. Рада познакомиться. Меня зовут Шина.
Oh, so have you already met everyone?
Ты уже знаешь всех?
Yes, during winter break.
Да, с зимних каникул.
Ah, except Minami-chan.
Кроме Минами.
Speaking of which, how long has it been now, Minami-chan?
Кстати, как давно тебя здесь не было, Минами?
Uh...
Ну...
Didn't Minami-chan come here in April?
Минами была здесь в апреле, да?
Yep! Pleased to meet you! I'm Okamoto Minami.
Да. Рада познакомиться. Я — Окамото Минами.
Pleased to meet you! I'm Shiina Yuuhi.
Я тоже рада. Меня зовут Шина Юхи.
By the way, I'm the manager, the cook...
А я — управляющий, повар...
AND garbage boy!
И мальчик на побегушках!
Onee-chan!
Сестрица!
Well, it's true ain't it?
Но ведь так и есть.
Yep, that's all my job. I'm Makihara Kosuke.
Такова моя работа. Макихара Коске.
Right.  Looking forward to living with you all.
Да, думаю, мне здесь понравится.
Alright, shall we get started?
Приятного аппетита!
Hey! I was going for that!
Я это хотела!
Let go!
Отпусти!
No way, I'm going for it.
Ни за что, это моё!
Hey!
А-а-а!
Bwahahaha...!
Фа-фа-фа-фа-фа!
Seconds, Kosuke!
Коске, добавки!
Really pile it on!
Давай ещё!
Here you go.
Конечно.
Sorry, Ai-san.
Прости, Ай.
No problem.
Ничего.
Ai-san, if you would please.
Ай, передай, пожалуйста.
Of course.
Конечно.
Hee hee. Well, isn't that strange.
Ха, забавно, не правда ли?
You guys talk back and forth like a married couple.
Вы ведёте себя, как муж и жена.
Y-You've got it wrong!
Неправда!
Yeah, she's right.
Вот именно.
It's just that we have known each other for a while now.
Просто мы уже знаем друг друга некоторое время.
Yeah, it's not like that at all.
Да, и поэтому ничего такого.
Yeah, she can't get married!
Она не может выйти замуж.
She is married to dorm life.
У нее просто нет на это времени.
Mio-chan!
Мио!
Well, it isn't surprising actually.
Да ничего удивительного.
Yeah, you guys really are always together.
Вы оба всё время вместе.
You guys are looking into it too much.
Вы придаёте этому слишком много значения.
Yeah, that's about what I thought.
Я так и думала.
Uh... Shiina-san you are in choir aren't you?
Шина, ты же в хоре?
Yes, starting this semester.
Да, с этого года.
So then you must be a great singer.
Тогда ты хорошо поёшь?
Oh, no... I'm not really that great.
Да нет, не очень.
Well, I can do this much...
Ну, я вот как могу...
Thanks!
Спасибо.
Wow, that was awesome!
Великолепно!
Shiina-san really is beautiful, don't you think?
А Шина красивая, да?
Yeah, no kidding!
Да, верно.
She is tall, pretty, and has great style.
Высокая, симпатичная и одевается со вкусом.
Chika, you're pretty and your style sense is pretty good too.
Чика, ты тоже прекрасна, и у тебя хорошее чувство стиля.
What? That's not true. Besides, my boobs are too small.
Вовсе нет. И груди у меня маленькие.
Hey, Chika-chan... are you an A-cup?
Чика... первый размер?
Yeah, 65-A...
65-А...
69-A...
69-А...
Twins!
Друзья!
I'm beginning to think they're getting too muscular.
Мне кажется, они становятся слишком мускулистыми.
Really? They look perfectly soft to me.
Разве? Как по мне, так они очень даже мягкие.
Hmm? I don't think so.
Да? А мне так не кажется.
C-Can I touch them?
Можно потрогать?
Well, I, uh... guess.
Ну... да.
Just as I thought. They feel nice to the touch.
Так и думала. Очень приятные на ощупь.
Can I touch yours as well?
А мне твои можно?
Uh, go ahead.
Конечно.
Uh... Sorry to interrupt.
Не хотела вам мешать.
D-Did I surprise you?
Я вас напугала?
Are you okay?
Всё нормально?
We're fine!
Да, всё нормально!
Oh, hey. The cat is taking a bath!
О, киска ванну принимает!
Yeah, Tara-chan loves the bath.
Тара любит купаться.
Oh, you're a little water snake.
Водолюбивая.
You're so little and cute.
Маленькая и милая.
So what do you think of this place, Shiina-san?
Шина, как тебе это общежитие?
Oh, it's great. It's like a home away from home.
Тут замечательно. Здесь я чувствую себя, как дома.
Yep.
Ага.
The manager's food is delicious, too.
И управляющий готовит очень вкусно.
No kidding!
Точно!
So what's up with Kaoru-chan?
А что такое с Каору?
She doesn't seem to smile much.
Похоже, она не часто улыбается.
I wonder if something happened to her.
Может, с ней что-то случилось?
Kaoru-san is always like that.
Каору всегда такая.
Yeah, That samurai thing is kind of her deal.
Ну, Каору такой вот самурай.
She isn't a samurai! She is a separatist!
Не самурай она, а одиночка!
Speaking of which, Kaoru-san is a sweet person, but I have never really seen her smile.
А верно, Каору добрая, но я ни разу не видела, чтобы она улыбалась.
Here you go.
Пожалуйста.
Thanks!
Спасибо!
Oh, delicious!
Вкусно!
Kosuke. I need some cat food. It's time for my meeting!
Коске, мне нужна кошачья еда. У меня сейчас собрание!
Yep! I just finished it!
Да, я уже приготовил.
Here you go.
Вот.
Thanks, Kosuke!
Спасибо, Коске!
Her... meeting?
Собрание?
Oh! Minami-san, there is an NBA match on TV tonight.
Минами, сегодня баскетбол по телевизору.
Oh, I don't want to miss that!
Не хочу его пропустить.
Speaking of which, sorry about earlier.
Извини за то, что за столом было.
I mean putting you two on the spot like that.
Ну, что ты из-за меня в таком свете предстал.
Oh, that! It's no biggie.
Ах, да ничего!
That aside, it really is nice to have a manager that is so good in the kitchen.
Но хорошо иметь такого искусного кулинара управляющим.
Not at all.
Ладно тебе...
Have you been here a while?
Ты давно здесь?
It hasn't even been 6 months yet. I've only been here since spring break.
Ещё и полугода нет. Я тут с весенних каникул.
Good evening.
Добрый вечер.
Good evening!
Добрый вечер!
Uh, Kaoru-chan.
Каору...
Yes?
Да?
Hey, what do you think about grabbing some tea?
Хоть чаю возьми.
Sorry, I have to practice.
Простите, мне надо тренироваться.
Kanzaki House of the 5-Arm Earth-Dragon Wind-Sword School...
Дом Канзаки, школа пятиручного земледраконьего ветряного меча...
She does kendo.
Это кендо.
Oh, so that's what she meant by being a samurai.
Так вот что значит для неё быть самураем.
She does seem like that.
Ну да, верно.
Be back later!
Пока!
See you later!
До свидания!
Shiina-san. Have you already been to school today?
Шина, у тебя уже кончились занятия?
Yeah, I only had two classes today.
Да, сегодня было только два урока.
W-What's that?
И зачем?
Eh, don't worry about it.
Да так.
Oh, is it for a concert?
Для концерта?
Nope. It's for the dorm!
Нет, для общежития.
Everyone seems so energetic, but Kaoru-chan never laughs.
Все живы-здоровы, но вот Каору никогда не смеётся.
Right...
Да...
So I...
Поэтому...
I'm gonna give her a great big comedic punch in the face!
...сейчас она у меня до коликов в животе смеяться будет!
Oh, so that's the kinda character you are...
Так вот ты какая на самом деле, Шина...
Oh, I'm definitely that character!
Да, я такая!
Now then...
Итак...
How about I make you a part of my ultra-secret plan?
Ты станешь частью моего сверхсекретного плана.
I have arrived.
Я вернулась.
Welcome back.
Проходи.
I'm going to have some water.
Я воды возьму.
Thank you very much.
Большое спасибо.
Hey, what was up with that delivery, Mr. Manager!
Никудышное выступление, управляющий!
You say that, but...
Тебе легко говорить...
You were supposed to say "What's up Kaoru-chan?" then I was gonna say...
Надо было сказать «Как дела, Каору?», и тогда я бы ответила...
We're home!
Мы пришли!
Hey, Kosuke-san. What is up for today's snacks?
Коске, а что сегодня есть будем?
Oh, welcome home!
О, вы вернулись!
Did you finally start growing a mustache?
Ты наконец-то отрастил усы?
What was that?
Что?
See? That was executed perfectly!
Видишь? Вот как надо!
Shit! Now we have to come up with a different plan for Kaoru-chan.
Теперь нам придётся придумать новый план для Каору. Блин!
What the heck is that all about?
Чего это они?
No clue.
Не знаю.
Shiina-san and Nii-chan were determined to get Kaoru-san to laugh so...
Шина с Коске планировали вместе развеселить Каору, и вот...
Ah! Delicious!
Вкуснятина!
Thanks for the food.
Спасибо за угощение.
It's the phone.
Телефон.
Hello?
Алло?
Bum-ba-da-bum!
Бам-ба-да-бам!
I'm Yuuhi.
Юу.
And I'm Kosuke.
И Коске.
I find that if I sleep on a beach, I sleep too long. {The following joke makes absolutely NO sense in English since it is Rakugo so I switched it up a bit}
На пляже, мне кажется, я слишком долго сплю.
Well, then you are a sandman! But there is nothing wrong with beauty sleep!
Соня ты! Хотя для красоты неплохо и поспать!
Oh, and how long is that?
А как долго?
Just once.
Только раз.
Just once? What does that mean?
Только раз? И как понять?
It's a mysterious question but you have to keep a balance!
Это неизвестно, сам реши правильно!
So how do we solve it?
И как это решить?
I don't know. I can sleep a whole week!
Не знаю. Я и всю неделю могу спать!
What? Well, then you are oversleeping, beauty!
Что? Да ты ж тогда спящая красавица!
Thank you very much!
Спасибо за внимание!
I'm sorry but it's time for practice...
Извините, но у меня сейчас тренировка.
They tried lots of things but nothing seemed to help.
Они многое испробовали, но ничего не получалось.
They spent a lot of time planning stuff,
Планируя всё это они проводили много времени вместе.
and all their time together started making them seem like old friends.
И они становились всё больше похоже на старых добрых друзей.
It's about 1 week until Kaoru-chan's birthday. We have to win this Performer Challenge before then.
Ещё неделя до дня рождения Каору. За это время мы должны успеть выиграть этот конкурс.
Wait... What do you mean "Performer"? Why...?
Что значит «конкурс»?
Oh, it's fine! Leave it up to me.
Да так. Я обо всём позабочусь.
Yes, 8 o'clock exactly.
Да, ровно в восемь.
Yes, I think it will be around then.
Да, думаю, я там буду.
Okay, understood. See you later.
Хорошо, я поняла. Увидимся.
Something wrong?
Что случилось?
Nah... They just said to come back at exactly 8 o'clock.
Они сказали, вернуться ровно в восемь.
Oh, I see. It's your birthday so they must be planning a party.
Ясно. У тебя день рождения, вот они и готовятся.
It would honestly be kind of embarrassing if they did.
Мне даже неловко будет, если это так.
Oh, it's fine, don't you think? They are all so kind.
Ну что ты! Они все такие добрые.
Yes, I am always thankful for that.
Да, я им очень благодарна.
Okay, all of my preparations are complete.
Так, у меня всё готово.
Excellent, Mio-chan. I expect no less from the Lord of the Cats.
Замечательно, Мио. Ты прямо кошачья королева.
Yes. You may bow before me if you like.
Ага, можешь даже поклониться мне.
Alright. That's a good girl.
Хорошо. Умница.
I wonder what Yuuhi-chan is doing?
Интересно, чем Юхи занята?
Honestly, let's just say it's going to be dramatic.
Ну, скажем, это должно будет сильно впечатлить.
Sorry. Could you wait and see?
Извини. Подожди, ладно?
Got it.
Ладно.
I have returned.
Я пришла.
Happy Birthday!
С днём рождения!
Thank you.
Спасибо.
Happy Happy Happy Kaoru-chan.
Радуйся, Каору!
Happy Happy Happy Birthday
С днём рождения тебя...
Congratulations.
...поздравляем мы!
Are those fireworks?
Фейерверк?
Happy Birthday!
С днём рождения!
Soooo cute!
Как мило!
But seriously, these getups are incredible!
А эти наряды очень хороши.
Kosuke-kun made them.
Коске сделал их.
I wasn't really sure they would hold up.
Но я не думал, что они будут держаться.
But it really puts you in the mood. Chika, should we grab our summer kimonos?
Это поднимает настроение. Чика, может и нам кимоно надеть?
Sounds good!
Давай.
Let's all go change.
Все переоденемся.
Even Kaoru, right?
Каору тоже, да?
I... uh... don't have a summer kimono.
У меня нет кимоно.
Don't worry about it. You can borrow one of mine.
Ничего страшного. Можешь у меня взять.
So then we all put on our summer kimonos and had a little fireworks display.
Мы все надели кимоно и любовались фейерверками.
It was the first time Chika ever saw Kaoru-san really laugh.
Чика впервые увидела, как улыбается Каору.
I thought to myself, Onii-chan and Yuuhi really are something.
Про себя я подумала, что Коске и Юхи замечательные люди.
Success.  {QCer's Note: we sure that's not supposed to be circle? looks like she made a circle out of what I think is a Sparkler}
Кружок.
Okay, so tell me. Why were you so obsessed with getting Kaoru to laugh?
Но скажи мне, почему ты так сильно хотела, чтобы Каору улыбнулась?
I really like playing the part of a comedy actress.
Мне нравится клоунадничать.
Girls need laughter in their life.
Девушки должны быть веселы.
Through bad times and painful times, everyone has to deal.
С тяжёлыми и трудными временами надо как-то справляться.
But if a girl can't laugh now and then it just isn't life.
Но что это за жизнь, если девушки не могут хоть иногда посмеяться?
Yeah.
Да.
There was also that it was just fun doing stupid things with you.
А ещё было интересно вытворять вместе с тобой всякие глупости.
After all, girls just wanna have fun! Don't ya think?
Ведь девушки хотят развлекаться! Согласен?
I guess it's because you're always laughing?
Юхи, ты всегда улыбаешься.
I'm always laughing so...?
Всегда улыбаюсь?
Yuuhi, I...
Юхи, я...
You don't have to say anything.
Ничего не говори.
Kosuke-kun.
Коске.
I'm gonna...
Я сейчас...
I-I'm embarrassed.
Я стесняюсь.
K-Kosuke-kun.
Коске!
I'm cumming...
Кончаю...
A dream?
Приснилось, что ли?
If you don't hurry you're gonna be late.
Быстрее, а то опоздаете.
I know!
Да знаю я!
Chika-chan, wait up!
Чика, подожди!
Have a good day!
До вечера!
See you later.
Мы пошли.
Now then...
Итак...
Kaoru-chan?
Каору?
Uh, I...
Ах...
See you later!
Я пойду!
Have a good day!
Удачи в новом дне!